[Music]
justs wow manic that ring is so
beautiful where did you get it from from
that 25 cent machine by the entrance
damn bro if Mindy says no Then she ain't
the right one for you and that gold
digging cheating [__] should die in a
fire I hope she rots in the seven levels
of Hell thanks bro it's been a long time
coming but I'm finally going to propose
to minda today so she can move in and I
won't have to keep getting on the bus to
ride to her house to [__] her butt a lot
not to [__] on your party Manic the
Hedgehog but Fury think Mom will let her
move in she stole the flat screen TV in
our living room 3 days ago y she still
denies it even when we caught her doing
it on camera in our
house
yo someone silence that [__] of a
camera oh my God is this a 30in flat
screen TV my daddy never lets me have
one of these leave it alone meny La it's
not even 4K guys you're not supposed to
use a real names remember and the
Hedgehog family is B rashit why do we
even hang out with those ugly [__]
come on gang let's hit the next house
before the neighborhood watch makes
another
round yeah well I'm doing it whether you
guys want me to or not that's why I
invited Mindy down here for a round of
mini golf yeah but what if Mom
says maybe I could help you with
that I don't believe it it's the
celebrity race car Lightning McQueen the
winner of seven whole pist 10 cups C
Lightning McQueen you'll really help me
take that [__] to Outback Steakhouse
everyone knows 16-year-old white [__]
love the Outback Steakhouse almost as
much as
Starbucks that's a great idea why didn't
I think of it but why are you guys
helping me because I'm a tow truck manic
it's my job to help people that are
stuck also you could say we know a thing
or two about what it means to love
another car made her don't love he only
[__] nasty little race cars
plus manic can I have a word with you
for a minute in private sure thing
lightning then get inside
me
good manic this SL M you're planning on
marrying do you truly love that girl how
could I not
she has two really big boobs and a [__]
ton of makeup we even dated for more
than 3 weeks once damn right on my green
[__] but you're going to have to try
hard to win her over why is that when I
was burning rubber at the race track
last week I saw her getting [__] by
three
cars and I think one of them was my
boyfriend made her but I'm not ready for
that drama just yet so I'm going to
ignore that part and help you now I want
you to fix you attention on these cherry
red cheeks you see this bumper sticker
on my fat car ass do you know what it
represents no well I'm not surprised
since you're not a car this bumper
sticker is like a wedding ring but for
gay cars you have to take the drive
manic what I learned from Life in the
Fast Lane is that if you don't speed up
once in a while other cars will pass you
it's as my other boyfriend Chick Hicks
always says if you don't put your foot
on the gas you'll never get some ass you
know what lightning you might be a car
but you're also a really cool dude
thanks for the pet talk
good hey hedgehogs want to see me fire
my rusty Towing cable 200 ft across the
parking lot and straight up Lightning's
ass
a
man that was so [__] awesome yeah I
didn't know a car could scream in pain
like that hey look manic it's your
precious bribe to be and she's only 11
hours late this time Mindy baby you're
finally here you had me worried there
for a mobious minute oh I wasn't going
to come my dad only forced me to when he
heard our spot with a but but golf
pretend like I'm not even here while you
found my boish daughers but like round
beef I'm just glad to be here
commemorating my late wife by playing a
nice round of mini golf that's School my
home skillet biscuit did she like golf
no mama [__] hated golf but she's
dead wouldn't it make more sense to
celebrate by doing what she likes
instead then this isn't about her she's
dead daddy says men makes the rules
because women are lame and provide
little besides sex and food
that's right and if daddy wants to play
my mommy's least favorite sport on Earth
then godamn it that's what we're going
to do Amen to that [__] wow M stad
you're so cool would you by chance like
to be the center point of my school
assignment on Hitler's rise to power
okay I wasn't serious that was a joke
calling out you your toxic
masculinity did you know that the Nazi
party was the first to establish laws
ensuring the protection of animals and
you're a hedge hug so do the math ad Al
says you're welcome [__] leave me now I
don't talk to anyone that wears pink I
am pink then I guess you are a failure
now run along you are not allowed to
talk to me ever again hey Mindy can I
ask you something across the street at
the Outback Steak House oh I [__]
love the Outback steak house because it
makes me look cultured since I can take
selfies there and upload them on
Instagram
good I will go with you I want a [__]
B
potato Mindy baby it's time time for
what lunch take a wild guest [__]
there's only one reason why I would
bring you to outb Steak House a blooming
onion no [__] as of now I want you to be
my girl oh my green giant I already am
your girl I mean no more dating other
guys I want us to go steady hey can I
get a 12 piece with ranch honey mustard
thanks
for here me and my bride to be are going
to have a romantic dinner tonight you
know what actually make that to go in
case she turns South daddy ain't taking
no chance on some [__] go steady but why
things are great the way they are Mindy
I heard you [__] three cars last week
we can't do not remove my hand
[__] we can't keep playing this game
it's as a good friend once said you
won't get any ass if you don't step on
the
gas what are you going to fart in my
mouth sugar tits would you marry me and
make me the luckiest Hedgehog in town oh
my God manik are you serious right now
serious as I'll ever be woman and no
pressure but if you say no you you don't
get to watch me play basketball anymore
that's stupid not to me it ain't come on
Mindy just think about what it would be
like you're proposing to me in an out
backst house no one has ever done that
before well it's happening now
baby so get on your knees and suck on my
17in celery stick oh no this is all
wrong what the [__] are you waiting for
[__] hurry up and say yes to this
pantless man
you know women in this family aren't
allowed to make choices on their own but
Daddy what if what if I want to make my
own choices many how many female
presidents have we had since America was
founded well maybe maybe I could be the
first I haven't laughed this hard since
woman promised they would watch the
Marvels and
didn't come on Mindy do your daddy a
solid won't you at least try the ring on
well I suppose I could after all it is
my fifth favorite color although it
might be a little big on me since I only
eat vegetables and weigh 3030 lb if you
don't count my 389 lb of silicone in my
chest that school [__] we just use some
duct tap later or some [__] I don't give
a [__] imagine it someday we'll have our
own place a mailbox in the front lawn
that says Manic the Hedgehog what about
my name your name doesn't
matter okay you love birds we're done
setting up the wedding altar at putt put
golf let's get this wedding started yo
fat boy mind coming over here and
helping me destroy the [__] out of this
blooming
onion
Now remind me again kids why are we at
the putt butt golf course not playing
golf we told you Mom our brother manik
is getting married today and he wants
you here to see that bad [__] he was
able to bag manic who the hell is that
oh Jesus Christ that scared the [__] out
of me I forgot I had a third one hey
mind's Dad how do I look like stingi
from Lazy Town well I feel like a
million bucks well you're not but it
doesn't matter I already said you could
marry my daughter in the trade off that
whatever money you do make for the rest
of your lives I get
85% look mama meny is coming down the
aisle in her wedding
gown oh doesn't she look so pretty mama
I wonder if I'll be as pretty as her on
my own wedding
day hey that's the ginger that's toaru
flat screen TV
yeah I know we should ask for it back
after the
wedding a she looks sad though look what
I've done to poor M mama I hate the
thought that my perfection makes her
feel less than perfect on her special
day who could blame her she's probably
having second thoughts because manic is
ugly but to be fair though she's not
really the looker either but honestly
can any girl will really look in the
mirror and say herself is
perfect well I can only speak for myself
yes why are you in a dress new redit
ain't going down like this I want a cool
wedding with strippers like the ones I
saw on MTV take those clothes off and
shake your boobs up and down for our
guests before I smack
you but this is my mother's old wedding
dress many do as the groom says before I
your father spanks you in front of
thousands of hold on one 2 3 4 5 before
I spank you in front of our five
guests
yeah man I bet I would be enjoying the
hell out of this if I wasn't a gay truck
used to tow or pick up damaged
Vehicles me too why is my daddy the
Buster because our brother couldn't
afford a real one now before we begin is
there anyone who believed that these two
underage children shouldn't be bound
together in holy matrimony and
taxes Mindy lower your hand you don't
get to say in this wait a minute I think
think this is a wedding mom what in the
world did you think was going on you
mean that thing on that pillow is really
a wedding ring I thought it was really
small onion
ring I object Mama sit your ass down
you're going to ruin my chance of having
sex a lot manik can't get married he's
only 15 he won't be 18 for like 12 more
years get your math right first [__]
it's 11 manic please listen to Rison 50%
of what's inside our house will end up
in the gaping ass of an adventurous
sexual
deviant mama stop it you're totally
ruining our game game you mean this is a
game yeah Mama we're only playing house
to prepare for the real thing you're
[__] wait so this isn't a real wedding
I'm not getting married come on [__] if
we got married we would have to share
all of our [__] you know I ain't letting
you touch my Xbox haha
oh thank
God but you know when you do get married
for real I would love to be invited I
mean if it's an outdoor wedding anyway
ins s a car I can't exactly go through
most
doors up everyone tam4 5 here I hope I'm
not too late for the
wedding I would have shut up sooner but
I was destroying a blooming onion at the
Outback
Steakhouse I don't believe it's D is
12345 himself with my wedding D is 12345
please marry
me oh come on this is supposed to be our
pretend wedding you know oh don't be a
salty [__]
manic I can't help that I'm a [__]
player now where's my best friend in
whole [__] world at Sonic bring that
blueberry ass over here
boy I'm right here Tamers hey Sonic
what's up Neil
I said NE
[Music]
[__] we're not going to kneel to you
we're not even Sonic Underground
characters and also weird cars so we
couldn't even kneel if we wanted
to what you got something else say
[__] please don't I can't swim because
I'm a
car
what you got something else say
[__] I for one me to my one and only
[Music]
God at least you're Smiler than that
race cow
[Music]
[__] oh no he ain't he ain't looking at
me he's looking at you
[Music]
[__] are you
stupid what is that that you are
wearing you [__] [__] Bobby are you
seeing this I got to beat this guy's ass
why are you even here no one invited you
[__] I [__] kill you [__]
bye this is what you
deserve sorry not
[Music]
[Applause]
to go
to
go
[Music]